onemodelplace.com 2016-03-05

# One Model Place - Privacy Statement

## One Model Place - Privacy Statement

As part of the One Model Place (Hereinafter referred to as OMP) pledge to our customers, we recognize and respect your right to privacy. This privacy policy statement informs our customers of the privacy practices employed in the provision of OMP's products, services and website.

Questions relating to this policy statement should be directed towards the OMP support team at [cs](mailto:cs@onemodelplace.com)[@onemodelplace.com](mailto:Webmaster@OneModelPlace.com)  

  * **Associated Agreements**

This Privacy Policy statement supplements the practices and policies stated within the Subscriber Agreement (and associated product Schedules). Please refer to these documents for more detail on the practices employed by OMP for the issuing of subscription services.  

  * **Anti-Spam Policy**

OMP does not employ the use of spam for propagating awareness of our products, services or special offers.  

  * **Informational Collection and Use**

OMP does not collect any information on customers without consent. As part of the service offerings, customers will be prompted for information when enrolling, downloading a product or requesting further information. No information is collected about a customer if just browsing the website. Details that will become public are clearly stated as 'public' in the enrolment process, Subscriber Agreement and associated schedules.

*“We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain  
anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use  
non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information,  
browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled  
over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide  
advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to  
you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to  
collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising  
practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit* *  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.>”*

  * **Subscription Registration**

When subscribing to OMP, you will be required to submit personal information as specified on the signup page. This information will be used by OMP to contact the customer about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest, including but not limited to product updates and associated promotional material. It also aids OMP in providing improved global services by collating general demographic information. Please refer to the opt-out policy described later in this policy statement.  

  * **Opt-out policy**

Members can opt-out from OMP notifications by logging in to their account and edit the preferences under the Email Notifications section (Settings > Preferences > Email Notifications). Alternatively, it is also possible to contact our customer service at [cs](mailto:cs@onemodelplace.com)[@onemodelplace.com](mailto:Webmaster@OneModelPlace.com).

  * **Information Request**

OMP provides the ability to request further information or ask questions to the support team by displaying email links throughout the website. If a customer elects to use such links they may be requested to provide additional information depending on the nature of the contact. Typically, such additional information may include further contact details, and in the case of technical support, additional information about the customer's PC configuration may be required to aid a prompt a accurate response to the query.

OneModelPlace.com™ Ltd. (OMP) is a Portfolio Hosting Site. The images and materials, claims and statements, expressed, implied or guaranteed by members and non-members on this site, are the sole responsibility of those individuals. All information accuracy, copyright credits, image copyrights and usage, and other forms of information are the sole responsibility of each member or poster. OneModelPlace.com™ Ltd. (OMP) does not guarantee, warrant, or confirm information posted to profile display pages or to the messages boards.

© 1996-2014 - OneModelPlace.com™ Ltd. (OMP) - All Rights Reserved - Reproduction in part or whole without written permission is prohibited. Sitemap
